seminarprojects.org 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy - SeminarProjects

## **Terms and Conditions**

**What personal information will seminarprojects.org collect from me?**

If you are simply visiting a [seminarprojects.org](http://seminarprojects.org/) site we will only collect what is logged by our web server. These include web pages you visit, your IP, what site you were visiting before coming to a [seminarprojects.org](http://seminarprojects.org/) site, etc. This is standard information collected by almost all websites and web servers. If you attempt to bypass or hack our security protocols our systems  
will collect additional information about you.

If you sign up for one of our many lists we will only collect your name, e-mail address, country and age group, in addition to the information above.

**What about the web sites that seminarprojects.org sites link to?**

Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are ‘clicking’ to another Web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

[seminarprojects.org](http://seminarprojects.org/) sites are called affiliate / content sites. Content means that the site is primarily informative. Affiliate means that when you click on a link to another where you can get information or purchase a product. Those web sites collect data about your visit. [seminarprojects.org](http://seminarprojects.org/) is not responsible for what or how that data is used.

**How will you know when our policy changes?**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If and when we do the day, date, year and time will be posted on this page.

**Questions about our Privacy Policy**

Please send questions to info@seminarprojects.org.
